JORGE SARRICOLEA

WEB DEVELOPER AND UX/UI DESIGNER



ABOUT ME



I am a Web Developer specialized in UI/UX Design, with 2 years of experience working on different projects. I am a Personal Finance and Technology enthusiast, always keeping up with the latest trends, and have the ability to learn anything I set my mind to.

Check my own web page!

jorgesarricolea.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Weather APP | March 2023 - April 2023

GitHub: Weather-APP

I have used the free OpenWeatherMap API with a minimalist design, and I have used the icons that this API contains. It shows an error message and ask the user to try again if they enter an invalid value.

Spotify UI Clone | February 2023 - March 2023

GitHub: Spotify-UI-Clone

I This is a static page (Spotify Clon) demonstrating my UI skills with HTML and CSS, I made this project for desktop version, it is not responsive.

Web Developer in Datamatic Software | June 2022 - July 2022

LinkedIn: Datamatic Software

I worked on the Front-End of an employee registration and management page for a United States company. Adding new features and connecting Air Table API.

Full responsive web app marketplace on Bubble.io | January 2018 - January 2022

jumwork.com

I designed the whole brand and user interface from scratch on Bubble. Integration with Stripe API and others in Back-End process. Work with differents plugins, like Sendgrid. I upgraded old pages to the new responsive engine.

EDUCATION

Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida

Ingeniería en Sistemas Computacionales. 2020 - 2024

Platzi

Interface Design Course. 2020 HTML and CSS Practical Course. 2021 Software Engineering Fundamentals. 2021 Frontend Developer Course. 2022

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, JQuery, Node.js, Jest (Testing), Bubble.io, Java, Python, Git, Github, VSCode, Boostrap, Trello, Notion, Slack, Miro, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Figma (Mobile First)